[{"answer": "Well, I think the President went to step by step in directly responding to the concerns of the American people.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "So what is your reaction to the President's speech tonight?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, look, I believe that number one we'll have to see whether this diplomatic effort is real.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "But he's boxed himself into a really difficult corner now, isn't he?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Well, look, Piers.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "It's pretty rum state of affairs, isn't it?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "I don't know if they're paralyzing him now, but it seems like they did for a while.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Are these two things slightly paralyzing the President right now?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, it's going to be tough.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "How does that work in reality?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "AY: It's not at all plausible.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Is that plausible?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "They got the basic technology of how to make it and how to made it to rockets, artillery, aerial bombs during the Soviet Union and from Czechoslovakia.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Do they buy it in from places like Russia, where do they get such a large amount of sarin or whatever it may be?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think he made a good point that atrocities occurred to know that there was something awful that happened, the gas attacks, you can't watch them without having a great deal of sympathy for the people.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Tell us what you liked about the President speech first?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Bashar al-Assad?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is, is that I think his plan now is to spare Assad to leave the regime in place, but at the same time he says, someone must pay for breaking this international norm, but he's really not willing to actually make Assad pay.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Do you think he should go in there and try to kill him?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not really saying that, what I'm arguing is this that what the President has plan is not going to accomplish what he says he's going to accomplish which is to punish Assad for this.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Targeted assassination?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "You hope that this Russian initiative works, right?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely, that's the constitutional manner you have to have Congressional authority before you go to war unless we're in imminent danger.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "So, you welcome the President's decision to go to Congress?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "If American interests were involved, American soldiers, American business, American citizens, a direct threat to an ally, a NATO ally, Israel, all of those things there's a lot of the American interest in the Middle East that I would say ...", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Is there any Congressional authority, any resolution you could vote for?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "So, far Assad is not -- he's preoccupied in his own country and he has another chance to reach out or lash out in other countries, if we bomb him or if we corner him I think there's more of a chance that he lashes out against Israel.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why do you -- explain that?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Don't use gas.", "docId": "130910pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "AUL: When you saw your people -- repeat the last part of that?", "qSentId": 183}]